Tldavison93@gmail.com

# Occupational Attributes

Over four years working various positions inside a large grocery store chain. Have always been more than willing to work as needed, whenever needed. Provide excellent service to customers with a great attitude and cheerfulness. I have also worked for a large banking company where the customers are the priority and becoming the better bank is key. Currently I am working at a Christian preschool where helping the children learn and focusing on their needs is top priority.

- Providing outstanding customer service
- Flexibility and willingness to cross train as needed
- · Easily trained for new positions
- · Eager to learn
- · Positive Attitude
- · Well Respected
- · Trusted by coworkers and superiors
- Honest
- Works well under pressure
- · Handles money well
- Responsible
- Computer skills
- · People skills
- · Excellent communication skills
- Well organized

## **Employment**

#### Ingles Markets INC. 2011 – 2015

**CASHIER** 

BOOK KEEPER - handling deposits, counting down and reconciling tills, overlooking cashiers BAKERY CLERK

DELI CLERK

SERVICE CLERK—bagging groceries, helping customers out, cleaning around the store FRONT MANAGER (CUSTOMER SERVICE) – preparing and delivering deposits, counting down and reconciling tills, dealing with customer complaints, putting customers first

#### TD Bank - Call Center

BANKING SPECIALIST 1 – providing excellent customer service while helping customers with their needs on their bank account, solving problems, data entry, proper phone etiquette

#### SolVerus Christian Academy 2015 -- Present

INFANT ROOM TEACHER

LEAD 2-3 YEAR OLD TEACHER – planning and implementing lesson plans to teach the children to meet certain curriculum throughout the school year while providing a safe and comfortable environment for the children

#### Education

Woodmont High School - Piedmont, SC

## High School Diploma - 2012

## Greenville Technical College

Early Childhood Education – 2013 to present

## Personal

- · Enjoy Reading
- Outgoing
- Soft Spoken
- · Well Organized
- · Easy Going

# References

## Lisa Branham

Former Teacher 864-350-4294 312 Sunny Lane, Piedmont, SC 29673

## **Debbie Norris**

Former Co Worker 864-630-8007 406 S Piedmont HWY Piedmont, SC 29673

## Melissa Sims

Former Teacher 864-505-1946 1025 Dunklin Bridge Road Ft. Inn, SC 29644

#### **Christel Scott**

Personal 864-363-2851 228 Southern Rd Belton, SC 29627